在我漫长的生命当中
ELlJAH: Over the course
of my long life...
我逐渐相信
我们的命运与血亲相连
...I have come to believe that we are bound
forever to those with whom we share blood.
我们虽无法选择家人
And while we may not choose our family...
这份血缘却是我们最强大的力量
...that bond can be
our greatest strength...
抑或是最深切的遗憾
...or our deepest regret.
从我有记忆以来
就一直陷于这不幸的循环中
This unfortunate truth has haunted me
for as long as I can recall.
（三百年前 密西西比河）
你怎么看？
What do you make of that?
没有标志，没有旗帜
No banner, no flag.
凭空出现
Floated in out of nowhere.
谜之船
A miracle ship.
为什么会一直停在那里？
Why is it just sitting out there?
不如我们去看看吧
I suppose we ought to find out.
人都去哪了？
Where in hell is everyone?
一艘废弃的船
Deserted.
所以船上的东西见者有份
Which makes everything
in the hold legally forfeit.
大家自己拿吧
Take what suits you.
这个你又怎么看？
What do you make that?
打开它
Open it up.
什么鬼东西？
What the hell?
你好
REBEKAH: Hello.
长途旅行之后见到这么一张帅脸
Lovely to see
such a handsome face
真是开心
after a long journey.
我能吃他吗，哥哥？
Can I eat him, brother?
我建议你别这么做
ELlJAH: I'd rather you didn't.
不用害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
照我说的做
You'll do exactly as I say.
你不会记得这一切
You'll remember nothing.
我不会记得这一切
I will remember nothing.
我们航行了好久
We have had a very
long journey,
途中，我们很不幸地
wherein which,
unfortunately,
失去了全部船员
we lost all of our crew.
因此，我们请求你帮个忙
Therefore, I would ask you
to kindly transport
把我们的东西运到岸上去
our belongings
to the shore.
你们究竟是什么怪物？
What kind
of hell demons are you?
我们是吸血鬼，亲爱的
REBEKAH: We're vampires, darling.
吸血鬼真祖
The Original vampires.
蕾贝卡，以利亚
Rebekah, Elijah.
我们的兄弟柯尔跟芬恩
愿他们安息
Our brothers, Kol and Finn,
may they rest in peace.
是要让我压轴出场吗？
KLAUS: Are we saving
the best for last?
我们同母异父的兄弟尼克劳斯
And our half-brother Niklaus.
别理他，他就是个野兽
Ignore him.
He's a beast.
从欧洲逃离，幸免于海难
We fled Europe and
survived the seas.
你愿意我一踏上新家园的岸边
Would you rather
I arrive hungry
就饥肠辘辘吗？
on the shores
of our new homeland?
尼克劳斯，你的行为总是这么
无与伦比
Niklaus, your manners are,
as always, without equal.
先生，劳烦你告诉我们
Sir, would you be so
good as to tell us
这里是哪里呢？
where it is that
we have landed?
法国殖民地路易斯安那州
The French colony
of Louisiana.
上岸之后的城市叫纽奥良
Off the shores of a town
they've named New Orleans.
非常感谢
Well, thank you so much.
我建议你为自己
Oh, I do recommend
that you find yourself
找个帮手拿行李
further assistance
for the luggage.
奉上我真诚的歉意
My sincere apologies.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：直到永远
（卢梭酒吧）
什么风把你吹来快活之都？
主演：约瑟夫摩根
CAMl: So, what brings you
to the Big Easy?
我以前在这住过
I used to live here.
真的吗？什么时候？
Really? When?
感觉像是一百年之前了
Oh, feels like
a hundred years ago.
我刚一个人搬到这里
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
I just moved here myself.
你为什么回来？
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
What brought you back?
我的弟弟在这里
Well, my brother
is here somewhere.
恐怕他已经给自己惹了一点麻烦
主演：克莱儿荷特
I'm afraid he might have gotten himself
into a bit of a bind.
你这语气似乎司空见惯了
主演：菲比托金
You say that like it's
a common occurrence.
他这人很复杂
Well, he's complicated...
目中无人…
Defiant.
粗野无礼、还有点喜怒无常
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Ill-mannered.
And a little temperamental.
我们不是同个父亲生的
See, we don't share
the same father.
当然了，我不在意这些
Of course,
that never bothered me,
但我弟弟却对此怨恨不已
but my brother
resents it deeply.
从来没找到归属感
Never felt
like he belonged.
总之，他总是容易惹上麻烦
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
All told, he has
a long history
of getting himself
into trouble.
我猜你总是帮他
And I'm guessing
you have a long history
解决麻烦
of getting him
out of it.
你弟弟惹上什么麻烦了？
What kind of bind
is your brother in?
他觉得这座城市里有人
主演：莉雅派普斯
He believes there are
people in this town
在密谋对付他
that are conspiring
against him.
自恋加妄想症
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
Wow.
Narcissistic and paranoid.
抱歉
我是个有心理学硕士学位的酒保
Sorry. Bartender with a grad degree
in psychology.
职业病
Total cliche.
听我说，卡蜜儿
Listen, Camille.
其实我来这里
是想找个人问一下
I'm looking for someone
who might shed some light
他正面临的困境
on his current
predicament.
她在这里工作，简安德弗罗
She works here.
Jane-Anne Deveraux.
知道她在哪里吗？
Any idea where
I might find her?
不知道，但我知道谁有可能知道
No, but I know
someone who might.
欢迎来到纽奥良
Welcome to New Orleans,
新月之城的明珠
in the crown jewel
of the Crescent City,
法语区
the French Quarter.
爵士乐、什锦饭、爱情，还有诗歌
Jazz and jambalaya,
romance and poetry,
更不用说夜幕之下的骚动了
not to mention things
that go bump in the night.
吸食人血的怪物
Monsters that feed
off human blood.
复仇心切的亡魂
Vengeful spirits
of the dead.
还有我最喜欢的女巫
And my personal favorite,
the witches.
这里是巫术店“灰色花园”
制片：兰斯安德森
Here we have the voodoo shop
Jardin Gris.
请进，体验一下巫术吧
Go in,
browse for a hex.
你要一直跟踪我吗，以利亚？
Are you gonna continue
following me, Elijah...
还是你想谈谈？
...or do you want to talk?
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
老是穿西装的吸血鬼真祖
Original vampire,
always wears a suit.
你们家族在女巫界很出名
You and your family are
famous amongst the witches.
尤其是…
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
Especially with
你弟弟又回来了
your brother back in town.
尼克劳斯来这里是因为他得知
Well, Niklaus is here
because he learned
有个女巫在密谋对付他
that a witch was
conspiring against him,
一个叫做简安德弗罗的人
someone by the name
of Jane-Anne Deveraux.
如果他要找简安，那他晚了一步
Well, if he's looking for Jane-Anne,
he's a little late.
你是说她已经死了？
Are you telling me she's dead?
跟我来
Come on.
她妹妹苏菲会希望跟你谈谈的
编剧：麦克纳度奇，茱莉普烈克
Her sister Sophie is gonna
wanna talk to you.
导演：克里斯葛端斯莫
那就是简安？
That's Jane-Anne?
在大庭广众下被杀让所有人看到
Killed in public
for anyone to find.
来这里的人都是女巫
Only people come 'round here
are the witches.
现在她妹妹来取她的尸体了
Now her sister has come
to take her body.
她的灵魂无法安息
Her spirit can't rest
until it's been
除非得到妥善的安葬
properly interred
in the cemetery.
拜托告诉我我弟弟跟这件事无关
Please tell me that my brother
had nothing to do with this.
无关，简安的死是因为施魔法被发现
No. Jane-Anne died because
she got caught doing magic.
什么叫施魔法被发现？
What do you mean,
she got caught doing magic?
你想知道谁杀了简安吗？
You want to know
who killed Jane-Anne?
你马上就会亲眼见到马赛尔的作为了
You're about to get your first glimpse
of Marcel in action.
吸血鬼马赛尔？
The vampire Marcel?
你们家族离开后发生了一些事
马赛尔也变了
Things have changed since your family
left town, and Marcel has changed.
我求求你快藏起来吧
I'm asking you,
stay hidden.
如果让马赛尔发现一名女巫
把真祖引回来
If Marcel finds out that a witch
lured the Originals back into town,
我的族人会遭到屠杀的
my people will be
slaughtered.
瞧瞧，我们发现了什么？
Well, well, well.
What have we here?
我得告诉你，苏菲，这个卫角
I got to tell you, Soph,
this street corner
今晚可不是你们族人的幸运之地
is not proving the luckiest spot
for your family tonight.
不到半小时之前
我们在这给你姊姊
Not half an hour ago,
we had to teach
好好上了一课
your sister
a little lesson.
我们在让她的灵魂安息，马赛尔
We're putting her
to rest, Marcel.
别来打扰我们
Leave us alone.
我可没允许你移动尸体
I never said you
could move the body.
事实上，我是特意把她留在这里的
Matter of fact,
I left her here for a reason.
以做逵
Send a message.
如果任何人想要叛变
If anybody is thinking
of joining some kind of rebellion,
我明确规定过女巫不准在法语区施魔法
my rules state that witches
can't practice magic in the Quarter,
但我仍听到风声说
and yet a little birdie
informed me
简安在偷偷地用魔法
that Jane-Anne
was cooking up
密谋些什么
something magically
delicious.
对了
Oh, yeah,
趁你们都在，我问一下
while I have you,
quick Q and A.
我的老朋友，混合种克劳斯
My old friend,
the hybrid, Klaus,
他突然冒了出来
he just happened to
show up out of the blue.
谁都不找，偏找简安
Asking for, of
all people, Jane-Anne.
有人知道为什么吗？
Any idea why?
我不知道
I don't know.
女巫从不插手吸血鬼的事
Witches don't get involved
in vampire business.
不配合我，你一定会后悔
That would be pretty stupid...
我向你保证
...that's for sure.
忠告你一句
Tell you what.
回你的餐厅去
Go back to the restaurant.
好好煮你那出名的秋葵汤
Cook up some
of that famous gumbo.
伺候好游客吧
Keep those tourists happy.
- 把尸体带走
- 什么？
-Take the body.
-What?!
不，不要，住手，马赛尔
No. Stop. Stop. Marcel!
我先暂时保管你姊姊的尸体
MARCEL: I'm gonna hold on
to your sister's body,
以防你想起来为什么克劳斯会来这里
in case maybe you remember
why Klaus is here.
马赛尔，求求你
SOPHlE: Marcel, please.
她的灵魂会无法安息的
Her body won't be at peace.
那可不关我的事
Not my problem.
你是想告诉我，过了这么多年
You mean to tell me,
after all these years,
- 马赛尔还活得好好的？
- 是的
-Marcel is alive and well?
-Quite.
我们兄弟好像卷进了一场战争
Our brother seems to have
wandered into a war zone,
但我还没能找到他
and I haven't been
able to find him.
马赛尔是克劳斯转变的
并在他的庇护下
Marcel, who Klaus sired
and brought up
茁壮成长
现在成了一群野蛮横行
beneath his own wing,
now rules a menagerie
吸血鬼的首领
of savage vampires
running wild,
在人类活动的地方肆无忌惮地杀戮
killing in public for
any human to come upon.
女巫们被控制了
Witches are held
in subjugation.
我怀疑尼克劳斯一点也不清楚
I doubt Niklaus
had any idea
自己卷入了什么样的麻烦
what he was
walking into.
抱歉，你刚才说什么？
Sorry.
What was that?
我一听到“我们兄弟”就恍神了
I stopped paying attention
at "our brother."
蕾贝卡
Rebekah.
我们那个令人憎恨
背信弃义的混蛋兄弟
Our hateful, traitorous bastard
of a brother,
他多次强调
who's negated
any sympathy
一旦我们离开他
I once had for him
by his repeated efforts
就得不到任何的幸福
to ensure neither you
nor I know happiness
我早就不关心他了
outside of his own
selfish universe.
永远在一起，蕾贝卡
Always and forever, Rebekah.
我们曾对彼此发誓的
That is what we once
swore to each other.
就当我反悔了吧
Consider this me
calling take-backs.
你这几百年也反悔不少次了
Oh, you've called take-backs dozens
of times over the centuries.
但当父亲找到我们
在这座城市追杀我们时
And yet when our father found us
and chased us from this very city…
我虽然很老了，以利亚，但我不糊涂
I may be old, Elijah,
but I'm hardly senile.
我很清楚我跟克劳斯密不可分
I know very well
I stuck with Klaus.
而不是三年之后，他用银匕首
And not three years later
he stuck a silver dagger
插进我胸口，让我一觉睡了90年
in my chest and sent me into
a magical slumber for 90 years.
你知道为什么吗？
Do you know why?
因为我有胆子离开他
Because I had
the audacity to try
过我自己的生活
and live my life
on my own without him.
够了，我觉得他有麻烦了
No. I believe our brother
is in trouble.
不管马赛尔和女巫之间发生了什么
So whatever is going on
between Marcel and the witches,
可怕得足以让她们冒险
it's dire enough that
they'd risk
把吸血鬼真祖引回来
bringing an Original
back to town.
是女巫把他引诱过来的
The witches
have lured him here.
我想知道为什么
I'd like to know why.
是你把我牵扯进这一切的，简
You got me into this, Jane.
给我力量去了结这一切
Give me the strength
to finish it.
门可以用的
The doors work,
you know.
你在施魔法吗？
You're doing magic?
我在对我死去的姊姊祈祷
I'm praying
to my dead sister.
来啊，表达你们的哀悼吧
Go ahead.
Pay your respects.
别给我添麻烦，苏菲
Ah! Don't make this
a thing, Sophie.
那个混合种在找简安
The Hybrid was looking
for Jane-Anne.
马赛尔想知道原因
Marcel wants to know why.
我想说你自己去问她吧，但现在不行了
I'd say ask her yourself,
but I guess you can't,
因为马赛尔杀了她
seeing as Marcel killed her.
我是以利亚
I'm Elijah.
听说过我吗？
Have you
heard of me?
是的
Yes.
告诉我你家人
So why don't you tell me
找我弟弟是为什么事
what business your family has
with my brother?
这里是圣地
This is sacred ground,
也就是说吸血鬼需要被邀请才能进入
which means vampires
have to be invited in.
但既然我已经孤注一掷了
进来吧
But since I'm desperate,
come on in.
我们可以在这自由地说话
We can talk freely here.
那你最好快说
Then I suggest
you start talking.
你姊姊想要尼克劳斯怎样？
What did your sister
want with Niklaus?
还不明显吗？
Isn't it obvious?
我们和吸血鬼之间有问题了
我们需要帮助
We have a vampire problem,
and we need help.
马赛尔有一支部队支援他
Marcel has an army
backing him.
女巫们一直想要反击
The witches have been
trying to fight back.
但我们运气不好
We haven't had
much luck
直到我姊姊简安过见了一个女孩
until my sister
Jane-Anne met a girl.
一个路过此地的狼人
Awerewolf passing
through the Quarter
她来自维吉尼亚的某个小镇
from a small town
in Virginia.
她和你弟弟有某种特殊的联系
She had a special
connection to your brother.
什么样的联系？
What kind
of connection?
很显然他们共度了一些时光
Apparently, they spent
some time together.
一切就顺理成章地发生了
One thing led
to another,
现在这个特殊的狼人女孩
and now this special
werewolf girl,
她怀孕了，她腹中孩子的父亲
she's pregnant,
and the father
of the child
she's carrying
就是你弟弟克劳斯
is your brother, Klaus.
不可能
It's impossible.
没什么不可能
Nothing is impossible,
尤其是发生在你弟弟身上的事
especially not when it comes
to your brother.
想一想
Think about it.
大家都叫他混合种，对吧？
They call him
the Hybrid, right?
带她出来
Bring her out.
你是谁？
Who the hell are you?
让我们单独说两句话
Give us a moment, please.
她们把你强行关在这里？
So, have they been holding you here
against your will?
她们把我引到河口，抓住了我
They lured me out to the bayou
and grabbed me.
然后施展了这些古怪的巫术
Then they did all these
weird, witchy tests.
我不明白这怎么可能
Not that I understand
how this could happen.
我是说吸血鬼没有生命
I mean,
vampires are dead.
他们不能生育
They can't have children.
也许如果你了解我弟弟的故事
Perhaps if you knew
my brother's story,
就能明白这是怎么回事了
it might explain
how this is possible.
请允许我…
Here.
If I may.
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
别紧张
Relax.
如果你对我敞开心扉
If you open
your mind to me...
我会告诉你
...I can show you.
最开始的时候，我们都是人类
In the beginning,
our family was human.
在一千年之前
A thousand years ago now.
快点，亨利，兄弟们又打起来了
Come on, Henry, our brothers
are fighting again.
尽管母亲对黑魔法有所涉猎
ELlJAH: Although our mother
dabbled in the dark arts,
我们充其量只是想要在困难时期
we were largely just a family
trying to survive
试图努力存活下去
at a time when it was quite
difficult to do so.
无论如何
我们过得很开心
And, for better or worse,
we were happy.
然而，直到有天晚上
That is, however,
until one night
我们最小的弟弟被杀了
our youngest brother
was killed
凶手是村子里最大的威胁
by our village's greatest threat.
弟弟
Brother!
这些人可以在月圆之时变身为狼
Men that could transform themselves
into wolves during the full moon.
我们的家人伤心欲绝
Our family was devastated.
尼克劳斯尤甚
None more than Niklaus.
父亲决心要保护我们
Desperate to protect
the rest of us,
于是逼迫母亲
our father forced
our mother to call
使用黑魔法，让我们变强
upon her black magic
in order to make us stronger.
喝下去
Drink!
喝
就这样，初代吸血鬼诞生
Thus, the first
vampires were born.
但我们拥有的速度、力量
But with this speed,
this strength,
还有不死之身，让我们异常饥饿
this immortality
came a terrible hunger.
尼克劳斯尤甚
No one felt this hunger
more than Niklaus.
他第一次杀人之后
When he killed for the first time,
看清了自己的本质
we knew what he truly was.
尼克劳斯
Niklaus!
我这是怎么了？
What is happening to me?
不，别过去
别过去
No, don't! Don't!
父亲，好痛啊
Father! It hurts!
他是个野兽，恶心的怪物
He's a beast.
An abomination.
他不只是个吸血鬼
He wasn't just a vampire.
他还是个狼人
He was also a werewolf.
狼人的诅咒就是这样
That's how the werewolf
curse works.
夺人性命之后才会放动
It isn't activated
until you take a life.
尼克劳斯是母亲和别人的私生子
Niklaus was the result
of an indiscretion
她一直瞒着我们
our mother had hidden
from us all.
他的亲生父亲是一个狼人
An affair with
a werewolf like yourself.
父亲对这背叛感到震怒
Infuriated by this betrayal,
要求母亲对克劳斯施咒
my father forced our mother
to cast a spell that would
压制他的狼人面
迫使他放弃
suppress Klaus' werewolf side,
denying him any connection
真正的自我
with his true self.
以利亚，以利亚，压住他
Elijah, Elijah.
Hold him down.
哥哥，别让他们这样对我
Brother!
Please don't let them do this to me.
快点啊，儿子，快
Do it now, boy! Now!
救我
Help me.
你爸爸真混蛋
Your dad was a dick.
顺便说一句，我叫海莉
I'm Hayley,
by the way.
既然你打算把你们的一切向我倾诉
You should probably
know my name
也许你该知道我的名字
if you're gonna tell me
your whole life story.
我知道你的名字
I mean, I know yours.
你的家人真是传奇
Your family is legendary.
你弟弟是恶名昭彰的神经病
Your brother is
a notorious psycho,
我还跟他睡了，真佩服自己
who I slept with.
Classic me.
我不能帮他找藉口
I cannot excuse his behavior,
不过你要明白
but you must understand
几百年来
that our father hunted him,
父亲一直追杀他
追杀我们
hunted us for centuries.
每次我们得到片刻欢愉
Every time we found
a moment of happiness,
就被迫逃亡，即使是在这里，纽奥良
we were forced to flee,
even here in New Orleans,
曾让我们最快乐的地方
where we were happiest of all.
在尼克劳斯破除了
Not long after
Niklaus broke the spell
阻碍他成为混合种的咒语不久之后
which prevented him
from becoming the Hybrid...
他打败了父亲
...he defeated our father.
我以为他会因此快乐
I thought this
would make him happy.
但他比从前更愤怒
He was angrier than ever.
我想，或许这孩子
I wonder if, perhaps,
this baby
可以帮我弟弟找回快乐
might be a way
for my brother to find happiness.
我回他自己
A way to save him from himself.
我很高兴你能那么想
I'm glad you feel that way.
因为我们需要你的帮助
Because we need your help.
你到底要什么？
What, precisely,
is it that you want,
这又跟这女孩有什么关系？
and what does it have to do
with this young woman?
我们要把马赛尔和他的吸血鬼们
赶出这个城市
We want to run Marcel
and his vampires out of town.
克劳斯是关键
Klaus is the key.
马赛尔所知道关于吸血鬼的一切
Everything Marcel knows
about being a vampire,
都是跟克劳斯学的
he learned from Klaus.
马赛尔信任他，仰慕他
Marcel trusts him.
Looks up to him.
他不会预料到他的背叛
He won't see the betrayal coming.
对，我相信你也知道
Yes. Well, as I'm sure
you're aware,
我弟弟尼克劳斯不喜欢被吩咐做事
my brother Niklaus
doesn't like to be told what to do.
所以我才带你来这里
That's why
I brought you here.
马赛尔几十年前把狼人
都赶出了这个城市
Marcel drove the werewolves
out of town decades ago.
你真的以为他会欢迎
Do you really think
he's going to welcome
一个混合种婴儿做邻居吗？
a Hybrid baby
to the neighborhood?
说服克劳斯来帮我们
Convince Klaus to help us
就不会有人知道真祖家族
and no one has to know
about the newest member
添了个新成员
of the Original family.
听着很像是威胁啊
That sounds remarkably
like blackmail.
我说过，这是孤注一掷
Like I said,
I'm desperate.
好吧，那么…
Well, then.
这事非我莫属了，是不是？
I have my work cut out for me,
don't l?
晚安，以利亚
Evening, Elijah.
尼克劳斯
Niklaus.
真没想到你不请自来啊
What an entirely
unwelcome surprise.
你的态度倒是意料之中啊
And what an entirely
unsurprising welcome.
跟我来
Come with me.
我哪都不去
除非查出
I'm not going anywhere
until I find out
是谁在密谋对付我
who's conspiring against me.
我已经帮你查到了
I believe I just
found that out for you.
不，不可能
No. It's impossible.
我也这么说过
I said the same thing myself.
撒谎，你们都在撒谎
This is a lie.
You're all lying.
吸血鬼无法生育
Vampires cannot procreate.
但狼人可以
But werewolves can.
魔法让你成为吸血鬼
Magic made you a vampire...
但你生来就是狼人
...but you were born
a werewolf.
你是混合种真祖
You're the Original Hybrid,
你族类的第一人
the first of your kind,
这次怀孕
是自然的一个疏漏
and this pregnancy
is one of nature's loopholes.
这一定是别人的种，承认吧
You've been with someone else.
Admit it!
嘿，我被困在一个
Hey, I've spent days held captive
恐怖的鳄鱼河口好几天
in a freakin' alligator bayou
因为他们认为我怀着
because they think
that I'm carrying
一个神奇的婴儿
some magical miracle baby.
要不是你的种
Don't you think
I would've 'fessed up
我不会坦白吗？
if it wasn't yours?
我姊姊献出了生命完成咒语
My sister gave her life
to perform the spell
就为了确认怀孕是真的
she needed to confirm
this pregnancy.
因为简安的牺牲
Because of Jane-Anne's sacrifice,
这女孩和她孩子的性命
the lives of this girl and her baby
现在由我们决定
are now controlled by us.
我们可以让他们很安全
We can keep them safe.
也可以杀了他们
Or we can kill them.
如果你不帮我们搞定马赛尔
If you don't help us
take down Marcel,
别怪我，我会让海莉活不到
so help me,
Hayley won't live long enough
可以穿孕妇装
to see her first
maternity dress.
等等，什么？
Wait, what?
够了
如果你想马赛尔死，他会的
Enough of this. If you want
Marcel dead, he's dead.
- 我会亲手干掉他
- 不
-I'll do it myself.
-No.
不行，现在还不行
We can't.
Not yet.
我们必须连循自己的计划
We have a clear plan
that we need to follow,
而且有很多规矩
and there are rules.
你竟敢命令我
How dare you command me.
用你自认为是
Threaten me with what you
我的弱点的东西来恐吓我
wrongfully perceive
to be my weaknesses?
这是个无聊的骗局
This is a pathetic deception.
谎话我听够了
I won't hear any more lies.
尼克劳斯…
ELlJAH: Niklaus.
你听
Listen.
杀掉她和孩子
Kill her, and the baby.
我才不在乎
What do I care?
管他的，我走了
Screw this.
I'm out of here.
谁也不准趣她
No one touches the girl.
我会想办法的
I'll fix this.
尼克劳斯
ELlJAH: Niklaus.
这是个圈套，以利亚
It's a trick, Elijah.
不，弟弟，这是个礼物
No, brother.
It's a gift.
是你的机会，也是我们的
It's your chance.
It's our chance.
什么机会？
To what?
新的开始
拿回我们失去的一切
To start over.
Take back everything we lost,
一切被夺走的东西
everything that was
taken from us.
尼克劳斯，我们的父母鄙视我们
Niklaus, our own parents
came to despise us.
我们的家毁了
Our family was ruined.
我们也毁了
从那以后
We were ruined.
And since then,
你一直想要的
all that you
have ever wanted,
我们一直想要的
all that we
have ever wanted...
就是一个家
...was a family.
我不会受人操纵的
I will not be
manipulated.
她们操纵你，那又怎样？
So they're manipulating you,
so what?
有了她们，这女孩和孩子
With them, this girl
and her child,
你的孩子…
your child...
可以活着
...Iive.
我会把她们全部杀掉
I'm gonna kill
every last one of them.
然后呢？
And then what?
你回到迷瀑镇
Then you return
to Mystic Falls
继续做那个今人憎恨的
to resume your life
as the hated one?
邪恶混合种？
As the evil Hybrid?
让人们畏惧你的名号
Is it so important to you
that people quake with fear
有那么重要吗？
at the sound of your name?
人们畏惧我是因为
People quake with fear
because I have the power
我有那个能力
to make them afraid.
这个孩子能给我什么？
What will this child offer me?
能给我力量吗？
Will it guarantee me power?
家就是力量，尼克劳斯
Family is power, Niklaus.
爱，忠诚，就是力量
Love, loyalty, that's power.
这是我们一千年前对彼此的承诺
This is what we swore to
one another a thousand years ago
在生活夺走你那仅有的人性之前
before life tore away
what little humanity
在自大，愤怒，偏执
you had left.
Before ego, before anger,
塑造了我面前这个人之前
before paranoia created
in this person before me...
我几乎认不出这个人就是我的亲弟弟
...someone I can barely even
recognize as my own brother.
这就是我们
This is us.
真祖家族
The Original Family.
我们会一直永远地在一起
We remain together,
always and forever.
我请求你留下
I am asking you to stay here.
我会帮助你，支援你
I will help you,
and I will stand by you.
尽到兄长的责任
I will be your brother.
我们一起在这里建立一个家园
We will build
a home here together.
救救这个女孩
So, save this girl.
救救你的孩子吧
Save your child.
不要
No.
马赛尔和他的吸血鬼们不受控制
Marcel and his vampires
are out of control.
必须采取一些错施
Something had to be done.
解决方法是引来更多的吸血鬼吗？
And the solution is to
bring in more vampires?
他们不是普通吸血鬼，爱格妮丝
Sophie: These aren't just
any vampires, Agnes.
他们是真祖
They're the Originals.
你凭什么觉得你能控制那个混合种？
What makes you think you
can control the Hybrid?
她不能
ELlJAH: She can't.
我也无法保证我能控制
Not entirely certain
that I can, either.
但现在你们女巫已经把他惹火了
But now that your coven
has drawn his ire,
我有个问题
I have a question.
怎样能让我弟弟不杀掉你
What prevents my brother
from murdering you
而是与你合作呢？
instead of cooperating?
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
那个导致我姊姊
The spell my sister performed,
失去生命的魔法
the one that got her killed,
并不只是确定怀孕这件事
it didn't just
confirm the pregnancy,
还把我和海莉连结在一起
it linked me to Hayley.
所以我身上发生的任何事
都会发生在她身上
So anything
that happens to me, happens to her.
也就是说她的命在我手上
Which means her life is in my hands.
克劳斯也许不在乎自己的孩子
Klaus may not care
about his own child,
但显然对你来说，孩子意义很大
but it's very clear what
it already means to you.
如果我必须伤害海莉
或者做更糟的事
If I have to hurt Hayley, or worse,
来确保你的注意，我会的
to ensure that I have your attention,
I will.
你竟敢威胁真祖？
You would dare threaten
an Original?
我已经一无所有了
I have nothing to lose.
在午夜之前，你必须让
You have until midnight
克劳斯改变主意
to get Klaus to change his mind.
嘿，兄弟，你去哪了？
Hey, man.
Where'd you run off to?
有人惹你生气了
Someone put you in a mood.
我能做什么？
What can I do?
你能做的是告诉我
What you can do is,
you can tell me what
你和那些女巫是怎么回事
this thing is you have
with the witches.
你知道我所有的一切都是你给的
You know I owe you everything I got.
但恐怕这事我们没得商量
But I'm afraid I have
to draw the line on this one.
这是我的事
This is my business.
我控制我城市的女巫
I control the witches in my town.
就这样吧
Let's just leave it at that.
- 你的城市？
- 一点也没错
-Your town?
-Damn straight.
有意思，一百年前我离开的时候
That's funny because when I left
a hundred years ago,
你还只是个可怜的小混混
you were just a pathetic,
little scrapper.
在那些压迫你的人的鞭打下
Still trembling from the lashes
of the whips
浑身发
of those who would keep you down.
现在再看看你，一方霸主
And now look at you.
Master of your domain.
城市王子
(MUSlC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
Prince of the city.
我想知道你怎么做到的
I'd like to know how.
为什么？
Why?
嫉妒了？
Jealous?
兄弟，我明白
Hey, man, I get it.
三百年前，你把这片
Three-hundred years ago
you helped build
鸟不拉屎的流放地建成城市
a backwater penal colony
into something.
是你起的头，但后来你离开了
You started it,
but then you left.
率确来说，你逃走了
Actually, you ran from it.
我坚持了下来，看看四周
I saw it through.
Look around.
现在是吸血鬼统治这个城市
Vampires rule this city now.
是我解决掉了狼人
I got rid of the werewolves.
我甚至设法摆平了女巫
I even found a way
to shut down the witches.
鲜血源源不断，狂欢从未停止
The blood never stops flowing,
and the party never ends.
你想加入？
You wanna pass on through?
你想待上一阵子？
You wanna stay a while?
没问题，我的就是你的
Great.
What's mine is yours,
但终究还是我的
but it is mine.
我的家园，我的家族，我的规矩
My home.
My family. My rules.
如果有人打破了规矩呢？
And if someone breaks those rules?
他们就得死
They die.
弱者才会手下留情
Mercy is for the weak.
这也是你教我的
You taught me that, too.
还有，我不是王子，朋友
And I'm not
the Prince of the Quarter, friend.
我是国王！
I'm the King!
给我放尊重点
Show me some respect.
你的朋友会在周末前死去
Your friend will be dead
by the weekend.
也就是说我打破了你的规矩
Which means I've broken
one of your rules...
可惜你杀不死我
...and yet I cannot be killed.
因为我永生不死
I am immortal.
现在谁说了算啊，朋友？
Who has the power now, friend?
他甘愿放弃一切
ELlJAH: He's willing
to give up everything.
醒醒吧，以利亚
这有什么好奇怪的呢？
Come on, Elijah.
Does that really surprise you?
我可以看得出
I can already see it.
他正步步得势
He's spiraling.
他肆无忌惮地发泄他的怒火
He's lashing out in blind rage.
上次见他这样发脾气
You know, the last time
I saw him like this
一发就是两百年
it lasted two hundred years.
那就让他耍性子
回来吧
Then leave him to his
temper tantrum and come home.
但愿这场灾难
With any luck,
this misadventure
能带给我们些许清净
will allow us a reprieve
from all of his insanity.
就差一点
He was so close.
当他听到胎儿的心跳
我可以从他的眼中看到
When he heard the baby's heartbeat,
I could see it in his eyes.
他想要这个孩子
He--
He wanted it.
他几乎尝到了幸福的滋味
He could almost taste happiness.
但是他的坏脾气毁了一切
And now his temper
has destroyed it.
即使我能让他恢复理智
Even if I was to return
him to sanity,
他也失去了马赛尔的信任
he just lost Marcel's trust.
看来
So....
我得赶紧去接那个女孩了
I'm almost out
of time to get the girl.
接她？
Get her?
你疯了吗？
Have you lost your mind?
我们是开孤儿院的吗？
Are we running an orphanage now?
你怎么说尼克劳斯都行
Say what you will about Niklaus,
但我以自己生命担保
but on my life,
我不会让那个孩子有任何不测
I'm not letting anything happen
to that baby.
你找到他就通知我
You find him,
and then you call me.
别担心，我知道怎么应付克劳斯
Don't worry.
I know how to deal with Klaus.
是这样吗？
ELlJAH: Is that so?
怎么不说清楚点？
Please elaborate.
以利亚米卡森
Elijah Mikaelson.
不用，我来，没事的
No. I got it.
It's all good.
是时候我俩好好聊聊了
It's time we had a little chat.
有什么要说的就快说
Well, if you're gonna talk, talk.
我还有事呢
I got things to do.
瞧你，一百年过去了
Oh, my, you have grown
quite confident
你变得这么有自信了，是不是？
over the last century,
haven't you?
我？是你和你弟弟变狂妄了吧
Me? I'd say it's you
and your brother got cocky,
来我的地盘就像到自己家一样
coming to my town
like you own the place.
这里确实曾是我们的地盘
Well, we did own the place, once.
回想起来，那时我们都过得很开心
We were all quite happy here,
as I recall.
但我们始终控制不了
Although we could never control
法语区那些烦人的女巫
those pesky witches
at the French Quarter.
你怎么做到的？
How do you do it?
你弟弟问过我同样的问题
Your brother asked me
the same question.
我也给了他同样的回答：这是我的事
I gave him the same answer:
it's my business.
法语区所有的一切都是我的事
Everything in the Quarter
is my business.
克劳斯非常友善地回到这里
Klaus comes into town
all nice and friendly.
后来开始对我所做的一切嗤之以鼻
Then he starts looking
down his nose at what I done,
就好像一切都是他某幅
Iike it's some cheap knock off
破画的廉价仿冒品
of one of his dumb paintings.
然后他就像个小贱人一样生气了
Then he gets pissed off
like a little bitch
咬了我的一个手下
and bites one of my guys.
对克劳斯这种不良行为我表示歉意
Well, I do apologize for
Klaus' poor behavior.
我想你该知道他咬一下
I assume you know
that that bite
会在几天内让你朋友丧命
will kill your friend
within a matter of days.
当然，尼克劳斯的血能治愈他
Of course,
Niklaus' blood would cure him.
什么？
What?
是的，显然混合种的血
可以治愈狼人的咬伤
Yes. Apparently, the blood of the
Hybrid will cure a werewolf bite.
相当方便容易的东西啊
Quite a handy little thing
特别是在需要谈判筹码的时候
when one needs leverage
in negotiation.
什么谈判？
What kind of negotiations
we talking about?
归还女巫简安的尸体
Return the body of
the witch Jane-Anne,
允许她的族人把她好好安葬
allow her people
to put her to rest.
你怎么关心起女巫来了？
What do you care
about the witches?
这就是我的事了，不是吗？
Well, that's my business now,
isn't it?
他的时间到了
His time is up.
你现在打算怎样，苏菲？
What are you gonna do now, Sophie?
我会照我说的去做
(SlGHS) I'm gonna do what I said
I was gonna do.
做什么？杀了那个女孩？
杀了你自己吗？
What? Kill the girl?
Kill yourself?
克劳斯不在乎那个孩子
Klaus does not care
about the child.
我在乎
ELlJAH: I do.
我带来了证据
我想帮你们的证据
And I bring proof
of my intent to help you.
你们已故朋友的尸体
The body of your fallen friend,
我从马赛尔那里要来的
which I procured
from Marcel himself.
简安
Jane-Anne?
愿她安息
May she be granted peace.
克劳斯会答应你的条件
Klaus will agree to your terms.
我还需要一点时间
I just need a little more time.
给过你时间了，时间已过
You had your time.
It's passed.
闭嘴
爱格妮丝
Shut up, Agnes.
先接受交易吧
眼下
For now,
accept the deal.
那个女孩和孩子要安然无恙
The girl and the child
remain unharmed...
否则克劳斯会把你们全杀光
...or Klaus
will kill you all.
我也会帮他
And I will help him.
难道我没说清楚我想一个人静一静吗？
Have I not made clear
my desire to be left alone?
每十年你至少会有一次
Well, you demand
to be left alone
要求一个人静一静
at least once a decade.
你的话已经不再有影响力了
Your words have ceased
to have impact.
你为什么一直叨念着那个孩子？
Why must you keep harping on
about the baby?
那个孩子绝对不会被生出来
That child will never be born.
事实上，海莉现在很可能已经死了
In fact, Hayley is
probably dead already.
你绝对不能就这样离开
You will not walk away from this.
放开我
Let me go.
休想
I will not!
别逼我再说一次
Don't make me say it again.
我不会放开你的，我绝对不会
I will not let go.
I will never let go.
即使我永世都得
Even if I have to spend eternity
拯救你，让你摆脱固执、任性
saving you from your own
stubborn, petulant,
卑鄙的自己
vile self.
如果我必须像父亲过去那样殴打你
If I have to beat you as
father used to beat you
来提醒你你的人性
to remind you
of your own humanity.
提醒你去关心一切
To care about anything.
你实在是太可悲了，以利亚
You're beyond pathetic, Elijah.
谁更可悲？
Who's more pathetic?
是那个盼望让家庭完整的人
The one who sees hope to
make his family whole...
还是那个
只能从自己的恐惧中看世界的懦夫？
...or the coward who can only see
the world through his own fear?
几个世纪以来，我什么都不在乎
I haven't cared about
anything for centuries.
你到底为什么在乎？
Why on earth do you?
因为我让你失望了
Because I failed you.
因为第一次父亲动手打你
Because the first time
our father laid a hand on you,
我应该直接打死他
I should've struck him dead.
我还向你保证过
And I made a promise to you.
家庭总是
Always.
Forever.
永远高于一切
Family above all.
你真是个多愁善感的傻瓜
You are a sentimental fool.
也许吧
Perhaps.
尽管如此，我也坚持了这么久了
不是吗？
But I've lasted this long in spite of it,
haven't l?
家庭的联系赐予了我们无尽的力量
ELlJAH: The bond of family blesses us
with an immeasurable power.
但是我们也要接受随之而来的一切
But we also
must accept what comes with it.
它带给我们无条件
无歉意去爱的
It gives us a responsibility,
to love without condition.
责任
Without apology.
我们永远都不能放弃这种联系的力量
We can never waiver
from the power of that bond,
即使受到考验
even when it is tested.
这种联系滋春着我们
给我们力量
The bond nourishes us,
gives us strength.
没有这力量，我们就一无所有
Without that power,
we are nothing.
这座城市曾经是我的家
我不在的日子里
This town was my home once,
and in my absence,
马赛尔得到了我想要的一切
Marcel has got everything
I ever wanted.
权力，忠诚
Power.
Loyalty.
家庭
Family.
我按自己样子塑造他，他却青出于蓝
I made him in my image,
and he has bettered me.
我要他的一切
I want what he has.
我要夺回来
I want it back.
我要成为王
I want to be king.
所以这孩子对你来说
ELlJAH: So, is that all
this child means to you?
只是夺权的工具？
A grab for power?
那对你来说意味着什么呢？
What does it mean to you?
我觉得…
I think...
这个孩子能够给你你一直以为
...this child could offer you
the one thing
你得不到的东西
that you've never
believed you had.
是什么？
And what's that?
家庭无条件的爱
The unconditional
love of family.
告诉苏菲德弗罗，我们成交了
Tell Sophie Deveraux
we have a deal.
你还好吧？
You all right?
只是吸入了灰尘
Just dust.
这地方真古老
This place is ancient.
是的，但这里应该够我们用了
Yes.
It should serve our purposes.
这是我们在法语区的庇护所
It's a sanctuary from
our business in the Quarter.
现在你是这个家中最重要的人
Right now, you're the most
important person in this family.
你需要一个安定的家
You need a good home.
我很好奇
So, I'm curious.
在这段时间里
有没有人间过你的感受？
In all this time, has anyone
asked you how you feel?
和一个疯子一夜情之后
About having a miracle baby
怀上一个奇迹般孩子的感受吗？
with a psychotic one-night stand?
身为一个母亲的感受
About being a mother.
我…
I....
我一出生就被遗弃了
I was abandoned when I was born,
我一变成狼，我的畚父母
and my adoptive parents
kicked me out
就把我赶了出去
the second that I turned into a wolf.
所以我真的不太知道
做母亲的感受
So, I don't really know how I feel
about being a mother
因为我从来就没有过好母亲
because I never
really had a good one.
我会一直保护你
I will always protect you.
我向你保证
You have my word on that.
高尚的以利亚向来信守承诺
And noble Elijah
always keeps his word.
搞定了吗？
Is it done?
事实上，搞定了
As a matter of fact, yes.
你见不得人的交易非常顺利
Your underhanded deal
worked quite well.
马赛尔非常高兴地接受了我的血
Marcel was only too happy
to accept my blood,
正如他接受了我由衷的道歉
even as he accepted
my heartfelt apologies.
他的手下提艾里还活着
His man Thierry yet lives
我依旧是法语区受欢迎的客人
and I remain a welcome guest
in the French Quarter.
我现在担心的
My only concern now
是那群无耻的女巫
is this coven
of impudent witches.
我相信她们是可敬的
I believe them to be honorable.
她们确实放了海莉
They did release Hayley to me.
尽管她们还没有完全坦白
Although they haven't been
entirely forthcoming.
马赛尔显然有什么她们需要的东西
Marcel obviously has something
that they need.
她们不想他死
They don't want him dead.
一定有原因
There must be a reason why.
我想外面风平浪静了？
I assume it's all quiet out there?
女巫们识相的话就不会使用魔法
The witches know better
than to use magic.
她们知道一旦施魔法我能感受到
They know I can sense it
when they do.
那些老家伙呢？
What about the old ones?
他们很危险
我不想他们伤害你
They're dangerous,
and I don't want them to hurt you.
真祖吗？
The Originals?
黛维娜，强大如你
Davina, as powerful as you are?
他们毫无机会的
They don't stand
a chance.
除了他用来
ELlJAH: In addition
to the secret weapon
控制女巫的秘密武器
he uses to control the witches,
马赛尔组建了一支小型的吸血鬼部队
Marcel has assembled
a small army of vampires.
齐心协力，我们可以从内部摧毁他们
Working together,
we could destroy them from the inside.
蕾贝卡呢？
And what of Rebekah?
她公主性子耍完没有
Has she stopped her
pouting long enough
要不要一起来找乐子呢？
to join the fun?
她已经明显表达了没兴趣
She has made her
disinterest quite clear.
我想是被插了太多次匕首
One too many times daggered
被关了太多次棺材了
and shoved in a box, I gather?
也或许她不赞同
Or, perhaps, she doesn't share
你坚定地认为我可以被拯牧的信念
your unwavering belief
that I can be saved.
蕾贝卡也许会给我们惊喜
Rebekah may surprise us yet.
毕竟我们都许下了同样的誓官
After all, we all
swore the same vow.
我希望她待得远远的
I hope she stays far away.
因为我想要收回这座城市
Because in my desire
to reclaim this town,
想要从马赛尔手中偷回他最珍视的东西
to steal from Marcel that which
he holds most dear,
我意识到最重要的一个弱点
I have realized one massive
vulnerability.
马赛尔最可能利用的一个弱点
One weakness that
Marcel could exploit.
是什么？
And what is that?
你
You.
原谅我，我的哥哥
Forgive me, my brother.
爱里没有权力
There is no power in love.
仁慈让你软弱
Mercy makes you weak.
家人让你软弱
Family makes you weak.
我要想赢得这场战争
If I'm going to win this war...
我必须孤身奋战
...I have to do it alone.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）